New York City police captured a cow on the loose in Prospect Park on Tuesday.
After the animal became an attraction for tourists while walking along the streets
and enjoying the park facilities.
The confused creature and camera holding humans stared at each other through a fence
for several minutes.
At other times, the cow wandered around the 526 acre park and the artificial grass
field normally used for human sporting events.
At other times, the wandered around the 526 acre park and the artificial grass field
normally used for human sporting events.
Officers used soccer goals to fence the animal in.
However, the cow then moved through one of nets, knocking down a police officer in
the process. Officers used soccer goals to fence the animal in.
the process. Police eventually trapped the between two vehicles parked on either
side of a baseball field's bench area.
Police eventually trapped the cow between two